bview.co.uk 2010-06-28

# BView - Privacy policy

##### 1\. Introduction

The services on this website http://www.bview.co.uk (or 'Site') are provided to you ('you'/'your') by BView Limited ('BView'), a company registered in England and Wales under registration number 6483387, with its registered address at 27 City Lofts, 112 Tabernacle Street, London, EC2A 4LE ('we'/'us'/'our').

BView is registered under the Data Protection Act, registration number Z1261666.

This Privacy policy outlines what we will and will not do with your personal information, and was last updated on 16th February, 2009. When we refer to personal information we mean information that refers to you personally, such as your name, postal address, email address or telephone number.

Please read this Privacy policy. If you register with us, or use the Site, you confirm that you agree to be subject to this Privacy policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy policy, please do not register with us or use the Site. 

The purpose of BView is to provide, via our Site, an interactive community of businesses and their customers (or 'Community') in order to improve the way that our Community members do business. We work hard to find the best sources of reliable information about businesses so that you can make the best decisions possible.

You can find, add, promote and share information about businesses that you own or manage, or businesses and people that you have dealings with. You can also build new networks of people and businesses within the Community.

##### 2\. Personal information we collect

In order for us to provide services to you through the Site, you must register and provide personal information to us. We store your personal information on our servers. All of our servers are located inside the United Kingdom.

We strive to minimise the amount of 'required' personal information that you need to provide us across our Site, but if you do not want to provide us with certain personal information, it may not be possible for us to provide all aspects of our services to you.

Your full name will be used when you send out invitations, notifications of reviews and follower notifications to any third parties. This helps our Community to engage with you.

We will also use your email address to send you updates on actions on the system, such as (but not limited to) when your business is reviewed, when someone follows you, or when you register with us. We also use your email address when a Community member wishes to message you via the Site. We never disclose your email address to others.

Information that you post on the Site may also contain personal information.

##### 3\. Business information

We believe that information about businesses should be freely available and freely exchanged. Such information may not be governed by UK data protection legislation and the provision and use of such information is governed by our Terms of use.

##### 4\. Anonymous information we collect

We also collect usage information from across our Site. This enables us to see how people use our Site. We analyse this information and use it to refine and enhance our services. We also use aggregated customer information to provide potential Partners with a general profile of our Community. 

We strive to ensure that none of this information can be traced back to you as an individual.

##### 5\. Why we collect information

We use the personal information we collect from users of our Site in the following ways:

  * to enable you to use any services that we may, from time to time, provide through this Site
  * to enable you to become a registered user
  * to send you information about our products or services, which we feel may be of interest to you, and to generally track the popularity of our marketing activities 
  * for general research purposes, to allow us to develop the services we can offer to our users
  * for Site administration (including enabling us to respond to any comments on the Site or feedback you may give us) 

##### 6\. How we use cookies

We use cookies to keep track of your identity and selections. This gives you a better user experience. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this, please refer to the help menu on your browser, however be advised that switching off cookies will restrict your use of the Site.

##### 7\. What information do we pass to other people, and why?

The success of our Community is based upon transparency and the principle of freely shared information. To do this we share the information that you provide to us, both about businesses and about you, with other Community members. We also use this information internally in the administration of the Site.

We strive to work with trustworthy data partners (or 'Partners') with robust data protection policies. However, we cannot guarantee the ways our Partners will use your personal information. The information provided to our Partners will be used by them in accordance with their own privacy policies, which may differ from our own. However, they are also under an obligation to process personal data in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998.

Any credit card information that you provide as part of the business ownership verification process, as explained in paragraph 14 of our Terms and Use, is sent to Barclaycard who help us to verify your identity. We do not retain this information.

We will also provide your personal information to government bodies and law enforcement agencies, successors in title to our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf.

##### 8\. Information you post on our Site

When you voluntarily register or post reviews, blogs or similar content, we will post information about you publicly. We will post your first name and last name on our Site. If you prefer, you can amend this to be your first name and last initial. We will also post your town, approximate age and a list of any business(es) that you have 'taken control' of on the Site. This information, plus any other content that you post on our Site, can be seen by any person that views the Site. This means that you may receive unsolicited contact from such people. This is beyond the control of BView. Please ensure that you do not post any personal information that you do not want to be made public.

##### 9\. Links to external websites

This Site contains links to external websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such external websites. The parties at these external websites are not under a duty to abide by this privacy policy. We strongly recommend that before you provide personal data to an external website, that you first read their privacy policy.

##### 10\. Security

The Site has security measures in place in order to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. We strive to protect your personal information, however, any information you transmit, you do so at your own risk. Once we have received information you submit to the Site, we take the protection of this information very seriously. We use 128-bit encryption, one of the strongest types of encryption, in order to protect your information.

##### 11\. Opting in and out of receiving emails from us

By registering on our Site you agree to receive emails from us relating to your activities on the Site as well as communications from us about new features and promotions, unless you opt-out. You may request not to receive future communications, system-based or promotional-based, by opting out at any time. Or, you can contact us via our feedback form.   

##### 12\. Finding out what personal information we hold about you

You may see, at any time, the personal information we hold about you by clicking on the 'my profile' tab. You can also change this information at any time by clicking the 'edit' links included on your personal profile page.

##### 13\. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with our Community, you can contact us at: 

**BView Limited**  
_Attn: Community Support_  
Loft 27, 112 Tabernacle Street  
London, EC2A 4LE

_Telephone:_ (0)845 680 2001  
_Fax:_ (0)20 7920 8088

You can also contact us via our feedback form.

##### 14\. General

This Privacy policy and our Terms of use contain all the terms of your agreement with us relating to the use of the Site. No other written or oral statement will be incorporated.
